Guide to the Gay & Lesbian Advocates & Defenders Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Public Affairs & Education, 1976-2010; Series III
  - Public Affairs
    - Press
      - News clippings/coverage
        - Subjects
          - Marriage
            - Massachusetts
              - 2001-2003 (Box 59, Folder 7)
              - 2004 (Box 60, Folder 1)
            - New Jersey, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 2)
            - Non-Vermont, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 3-6)
            - Vermont, 1997-2000 (Box 61, Folder 1-6)
          - Military, Gays in the, 1990-1991 (Box 61, Folder 7)
          - National gay rights advocates, 1989-1991 (Box 61, Folder 8)
          - National overview, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 9)
          - New York City rights bill, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 10)
          - Northeastern University discrimination, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 11)
          - Older gays, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 12)
          - Outing, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 13)
          - Parenting, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 14)
          - Public sex complaints, 1986-1989 (Box 61, Folder 15)
          - St. Patrick's Day parade, 1992-1996 (Box 61, Folder 16-17)
          - Scondras, David/ Boston Herald /Committee for Civil Liberties and Sexual Freedom (CLSF), 1987 (Box 62, Folder 1)
          - Slander and public homophobia, 1988-1990 (Box 62, Folder 2)
          - Speaking engagements, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 3)
          - STDs (sexually transmitted diseases), 1988 (Box 62, Folder 4)
          - Strawinski v. Greenway Irrigation Company, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 5)
          - Strikes, 1986-1990 (Box 62, Folder 6)
          - Television condom ads, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 7)
          - Tufts University, 1989-1990 (Box 62, Folder 8)
          - World AIDS Day, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 9)
          - Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - Photographs
        - Abbott, Sidney, Circa 1997 (Box 62, Folder 11)
        - Bonauto, Mary, Undated (Box 62, Folder 12)
        - Unidentified, Undated (Box 62, Folder 13)
      - Web site profiles (gay marriage), 2001 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Publications
      - Annual reports, 1978-2005 (Box 62, Folder 15-18)
      - Brochures
        - Promotional, Circa 2000-2008 (Box 63, Folder 1)
        - Public education, Undated (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Educational resources
        Consists of fact sheets, pamphlets, booklets, and brochures on various legal issues.
        - List of materials available, Undated (Box 63, Folder 3)
        - "Adoption: Questions and Answers", 2003, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 4)
        - "Anti-LGBT Violence", 2008 (Box 63, Folder 5)
        - Benefits, 2004-2009 (Box 63, Folder 6)
        - Child custody, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 7)
        - Civil unions, 2001-2006 (Box 63, Folder 8)
        - Co-ownership, Undated (Box 63, Folder 9)
        - Domestic partnership, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 10)
        - Domestic violence, 1992-1999 (Box 63, Folder 11)
        - HIV, 1997-2003 (Box 63, Folder 12)
        - Housing discrimination, 2002-2003 (Box 63, Folder 13)
        - Immigration and binational couples, 1991-2006 (Box 63, Folder 14)
        - Lesbian and gay rights (general), 1995-1996 (Box 63, Folder 15)
        - Marriage, Circa 1998-2008 (Box 64, Folder 1-3)
        - Massachusetts sex offender registry, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 4)
        - Parenting, families and adoption, 1993-2005 (Box 64, Folder 5-6)
        - Prisoners, 1992-2008 (Box 64, Folder 7)
        - Schools and youth, 1995-2008 (Box 64, Folder 8)
        - State
          - HIV overviews, 2002-2008 (Box 65, Folder 1)
          - Law overviews, 2004-2008 (Box 65, Folder 2-3)
        - Transgender
          - Legal issues, 2002-2008 (Box 65, Folder 4)
          - Rights, 1995-2008 (Box 65, Folder 5)
        - Workplace and benefits, 1999-2008 (Box 65, Folder 6-7)
      - Flyers, 1986-2010 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Histories of GLAD, 1978-2010 (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - Information card, "Your Rights if You are Arrested", Undated (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - Newsletters
        - AIDS Law Flash, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 1)
        - GLAD Briefs, 1979-2005 (Box 66, Folder 2-3)
        - GLAD Discovery, 1996-1997 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Posters, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Education
    - General
      - Accessibility, TTY (text telephone), 1995 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Assessment, planning, policy, 1996-1997 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Calendar, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Transgender outreach and services, 1997 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Volunteer and public education budget, 1994-1996 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Craig Bailey files
      - General
        - Correspondence, 1992, undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
        - Press, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 7)
        - News clippings, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Topical
        - Anti-discrimination forum, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 9)
        - Anti-violence, 1991-1992 (Box 67, Folder 10)
        - Bay Windows, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 11)
        - "Boys, Bathrooms and Bushes", 1992 (Box 67, Folder 12)
        - Cases, news clippings, 1985-1991 (Box 67, Folder 13)
        - Completed press forms, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 14)
        - Cutting, Ginny, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 15)
        - Families of the '90s, 1991-1992 (Box 67, Folder 16)
        - "Fenway Community Health Annual Report", 1992 (Box 67, Folder 17)
        - Fraternity settlement, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 18)
        - Gays in the military, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 19)
        - Health care proxy, Massachusetts, Undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
        - "Invisible Minority On the Job", 1991 (Box 68, Folder 2)
        - Massachusetts Commission Against Discrimination (MCAD)
          - Press, 1990-1991 (Box 68, Folder 3)
          - Procedure, complaint forms, Undated (Box 68, Folder 4)
        - Medical consent panel, 1991 (Box 68, Folder 5)
        - Miller, Tim, performance, Undated (Box 68, Folder 6)
        - Parenting and children, 1991 (Box 68, Folder 7)
        - Public accommodations
          - Flyer with definition, Undated (Box 68, Folder 8)
          - Settlement, 1991 (Box 68, Folder 9)
        - Violence, 1991 (Box 68, Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous printed material, 1990-1992 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Forums
      Consists primarily of promotional flyers and correspondence.
      - "AIDS Legal and Policy Issues", 1987 (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - "AIDS: The Legal Issues", 1988 (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - "Anti-Lesbian and Gay Hate Crimes", Undated (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - "Civil Rights and the Emergence of the Lesbian and Gay Rights Movement in South Africa", 1991 (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - "Employment Discrimination", 1992 (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - "Ford Hall Marriage Forum", 2002 (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - "Lawrence Human Rights Week and Gay Pride", 1999 (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - "Legal Issues Facing Families of the '90's", 1994 (Box 68, Folder 19)
      - "Lesbian and Gay Families", 1988, undated (Box 68, Folder 20)
      - "Lesbian and Gay Family Law", 1989 (Box 68, Folder 21)
      - "Living Well", 1991 (Box 68, Folder 22)
      - "Looking Back: 1978 - Our Struggles Revisited", 1988 (Box 68, Folder 23)
      - "Medical Consent: Who Decides", 1991 (Box 68, Folder 24)
      - "Networking Summit", 1998 (Box 68, Folder 25)
      - "New England Marriage Summit", 1996 (Box 68, Folder 26)
      - "Police Entrapment and Harassment", 1984 (Box 68, Folder 27)
      - "Public Sex Outreach", 1993 (Box 68, Folder 28)
      - "Rest Stops", 1984 (Box 68, Folder 29)
      - "Sex and the Law", 1989 (Box 68, Folder 30)
      - "Taking Care of Business for Gay and Lesbian Families", 1998 (Box 68, Folder 31)
      - "U.S. Commission on Civil Rights", 1998 (Box 68, Folder 32)
      - "U.S. Immigration Law and Gay and Lesbian People", 1989 (Box 68, Folder 33)
    - InfoLine
      - Grant reporting, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 34)
      - Intake
        - Expansion project, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 35)
        - Form, blank, Pre-1997 (Box 68, Folder 36)
        - Form, information request, Undated (Box 68, Folder 37)
        - Presentation, 1992-1995 (Box 68, Folder 38)
        - Resource lists
          - General, 1993-1994 (Box 68, Folder 39)
          - Adoption placement, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 40)
          - College organizations, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 41)
          - Criminal referrals, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 42)
          - District Attorney Victim and Witness programs, Undated (Box 69, Folder 1)
          - Domestic violence, Undated (Box 69, Folder 2)
          - Fight the Right, Undated (Box 69, Folder 3)
          - Human rights commissions, Undated (Box 69, Folder 4)
          - Immigration, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 5)
          - Mentally ill, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 6)
          - Military, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 7)
          - National AIDS Communications Roundtable, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 8)
          - Prisoner resources, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 9)
          - Transgender, attorneys for, in Vermont, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 10)
          - Vermont area, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 11)
        - Statistics, 1991-1997 (Box 69, Folder 12-15)
        - Training materials and schedules, 1993-1997, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 16-21)
      - Volunteers
        - Forms (samples), 1998 (Box 69, Folder 22)
        - Training manuals
          - General
            - 1995 (Box 70, Folder 1-3)
            - 1996 (Box 70, Folder 4)
            - 1998 (Box 70, Folder 5)
            - 2008 (Box 70, Folder 6)
          - Civil Rights, Undated (Box 71, Folder 1-2)
          - Hotline and Lawyer Referral Services, Undated (Box 71, Folder 3-4)
          - Information for violence and harassment calls, Undated (Box 71, Folder 5)
          - Intake volunteer guidelines, Undated (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Legal Referral Services (LRS)
      - Applications and information, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Cancellations from lawyers, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - Fees, 1997 (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - Forms
        - Blank, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 10)
        - Drafts with committee memos and notes, 1995-1996 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Inquiries from lawyers, 1996-1997 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Lists and directories
        - General
          - Attorney referral archives, 1988-1996 (Box 72, Folder 3)
          - LRS phone lists, 1997 (Box 72, Folder 4)
          - Massachusetts attorney directory, Undated (Box 72, Folder 5)
          - National Attorneys' Directory for Lesbian and Gay Rights, 1981-1988 (Box 72, Folder 6-9)
          - "New England Attorneys Directory for Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Civil Rights", 1995-1996 (Box 73, Folder 1)
        - Topical
          - Bilingual attorney referral list, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 2)
          - Transgender referrals and contacts, 1993-1997 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Notes and address book, Jenny Alexander, Undated (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Recruiting, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - "Report on First Year Activity", 1997 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Rules and agreement, draft, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Samples of, 1994-1995 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Maine
    - Concerned Maine Families (CMF)
      - Campaign materials, 1994-1996 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Candidate survey, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Cosby, C., speech at USM Conservative League
        - Memorandum, 1993 November (Box 74, Folder 3)
        - Audiorecording, 1993 November 10; 1 (Box 93)
          Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
    - Maine Won't Discriminate (MWD)
      - General files, 1994-1995 (Box 74, Folder 4-6)
      - Focus group transcripts, 1995 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Fundraising plan, 1995 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - News clippings, 1995 (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - Polling consultants, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 10)
      - Publicity packet, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Referendums
      - General
        - News clippings, 1993-1995 (Box 75, Folder 2-5)
        - Marco, Tony, "Special Class Protections for Gays: A Question of Behavior and Consequences", 1991-1994 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - First (MR1)
        - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 75, Folder 7)
        - Intervening groups, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 1)
        - Organizing effort, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 2)
        - Research, justiciability, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 3)
        - Wyman v. Secretary of State, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Second (MR2)
        - General file, 1993-1994 (Box 76, Folder 5)
        - Concerned Maine Families
          - News insert response, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 6)
          - PAC (political action committee) filings, 1993-1994 (Box 76, Folder 7)
        - Fein, Bruce (memoranda regarding), 1995 (Box 76, Folder 8)
        - Market decisions reports, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 9)
        - Op-ed piece, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 1)
        - Post-election
          - Complaint, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 2)
          - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 3)
          - Research, voter intent, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 4)
          - Secretary of State summary, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 5)
          - Working file, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 6)
        - Research, repeal with animus, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 7)
        - Signature correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Speaking engagements
    - General
      - Reports, 1995-1997 (Box 78, Folder 1-3)
      - Summary, 1983-1984 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous, 1993-1996, undated (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Topical
      - AIDS/HIV (Spanish), 1995-1998 (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA), 1985-1989 (Box 78, Folder 7)
      - Anti-gay harassment, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 8)
      - Community cable access show, MAHA, "HIV in the Workplace" (Spanish), 1998 (Box 78, Folder 9)
      - Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Speakers Bureau of Boston (GLBSB), speaker training, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 10)
      - "Governor's 1986 Conference on Disability Issues, Joining Forces: Civil Rights and the Disability Movement", 1987 (Box 78, Folder 11)
      - Lavender Law Forum (Kevin Cathcart), 1986-1990 (Box 78, Folder 12)
      - Marriage, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 13)
      - Massachusetts Continuing Legal Education, Inc. (MCLE) gay rights law training, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 14)
      - National Association of Social Workers, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 15)
      - Transgender murder community meeting, 1998 (Box 78, Folder 16)
      - Tri-City Conference, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Volunteers (general)
    - Application form, Undated (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Program evaluation, 1992-1994 (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - Recruitment, 1993-1997 (Box 78, Folder 20-21)
  - Coalitions
    - Boston National Voices
      - General file, 1999-2000 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - Boston Fire Department, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - Building Bridges Across Bigotry, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - Community Disorders Unit (CDU) meetings, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - Community Unity
        - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 5)
        - Membership and materials, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence and contact list, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 7)
      - Events
        - Chasen Morey event, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 8)
        - Firefighters' event, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 9)
        - Heifitz breakfast, 2001 May (Box 79, Folder 10)
      - Fenway Community Health Center, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 11)
      - Freedom to Marry Coalition, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 12)
      - Gay conversion response letters, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 13)
      - Grants
        - Eliot Foundation grant, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 14)
        - Greely Foundation proposal, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 15)
        - Haymarket People's Fund grant application, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 16)
        - Peace Development Fund letter of intent, draft, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 17)
        - Pridelights Foundation proposal, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 18)
      - Letterhead design, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - Membership, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - Mission statement, Undated (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - National Conference for Community and Justice (NCCJ) youth leadership nomination, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - Unity Alert
        - Fact sheet, Undated (Box 80, Folder 5)
        - Funding, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 6)
        - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority (MBTA) hearings, 2001 May (Box 80, Folder 7)
        - Project file, 1999-2001 (Box 80, Folder 8)
        - School violence flyer, 2001 March (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Community Works
      - General files
        - 1987-1988 (Box 80, Folder 10-13)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 81, Folder 1-4)
        - 1991-1992 (Box 82, Folder 1-4)
      - Annual report, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - Background information, 1981-1984 (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Extra Share, 1989-1991 (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - Honoree letter, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 8)
      - Media/press, 1991-1992 (Box 82, Folder 9)
      - Membership, 1990-1993 (Box 82, Folder 10)
      - On-going (blank forms and disbursement acknowledgment), 1991 (Box 82, Folder 11)
      - Payroll deduction, 1989-1991 (Box 82, Folder 12)
- Development, 1982-2003; Series IV
  This series consists primarily of a limited number of appeals to members and grant proposals, documenting GLAD fundraising activities.
  - Donations
    - Appeals, 1994-1998 (Box 84, Folder 1-4)
    - Direct mail packet samples, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Donor survey, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Event brochures and invitations, 1998-2003 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - "GLAD Summer Party", 1996 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - GLAD summer party brochures, 1997-2003 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - GLAD winter party brochures, 1997-2003 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Mailing list policy, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Marketing, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Memoranda, 1999 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Planned Giving Program, Undated (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Prospecting, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Grants
    - AIDS Law Project (ALP) grant proposals, 1995 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Meetings, 1995 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Proposals, 1994-1995 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - "Safe Schools for All Youth", 1997 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Non-GLAD Publications, 1973-2006; Series V
  The series is arranged alphabetically by organization name or publication title.
  The series consists primarily of newsletters, flyers and brochures published by various lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender local and national organizations and documents local and national issues confronted by the community.
  - Access Now Coalition, 1999 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Advocacy Institute, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Action Committee, 1991-1995 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - AIDS Coalition to Unleash Power (ACTUP), 1990 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - AIDS Policy and Law, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - AIDS Treatment News, 1987-1991 (Box 86, Folder 3-4)
  - AIDS Weekly, 1992-1993 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Alliance of Gays, Lesbians and Supporters (AGLAS), Undated (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Alliance of Massachusetts Asian Lesbians and Gay Men (AMALGM), 1988-1991 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - American Association of Physicians for Human Rights (AAPHR), 1987 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - American Association of State Social Work Boards (AASSWB), 1988 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - American Bar Association (ABA), 2005 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), ACLU News, 1985-1987 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) Lesbian and Gay Rights Chapter, Newsletter, 1986-1991 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - American Foundation for AIDS Research (AmFAR), Undated (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - American Friends Service Committee (AFSC), 1982, 1990, circa 2005 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - American Library Association, Gay Task Force, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - American Red Cross, Undated (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - American Society of Notaries, 1986, 1991-1992 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Amnesty International, Undated (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Anti-Defamation League (ADL), 1998 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Association of State and Territorial Health Officials Foundation (ASTHO), 1985 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Astraea Lesbian Foundation for Justice, "Threads", 2004-2005 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Barbara Roberts for Governor, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Be All Weekend, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Betty Taymor Fund, Undated (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Billy Defrank Community Center, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Bisexual Resource Center, Undated (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Bisexual, Lesbian and Gay People's Union of California State University, Options, 1982 January (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Black Gay and Lesbian Leadership Forum, Undated (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Boston AIDS Consortium (BAC), 1994 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Boston Alliance Against Registration and the Draft, Rough Draft, 1984 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Boston Asian Gay Men and Lesbians (BAGMAL), BAGMAL Newsletter, 1987-1988 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Boston Bisexual Men's Network (BBMN), The Bi-Monthly, 1987 February (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Boston Bisexual Women's Network (BBWN), Bi-Women, 1988-2000 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Boston Children's Services (BCS), 1993, undated (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Boston Gay Men's Chorus (BGMC), 1997 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Boston Human Rights Commission, Undated (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Boston Intercollegiate Lesbian and Gay Alliance, The Intercollegiate, 1986 December-1987 February (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Boston Lesbian and Gay Communities Funding Partnership, Undated (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Boston Lesbian and Gay Political Alliance (BL/GPA), 1983-1985, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Boston People's Music, 1985 May (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Boulton and Park Society, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - California Lawyers for Individual Freedom (CaLIF), 1985 February (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Cambridge Lesbian and Gay Alliance (CLGA), 1985 June (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Cambridge Problem Center, Undated (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Campaign to End Homophobia, Circa 1990 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Center, The, Circa 1991 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Center for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), 1993 July (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Center for Lesbian and Gay Studies in Religion and Ministry (CLGS), 2004-2005 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Citizens Alliance for Gay and Lesbian Rights (CAGLR), 1986-1987 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Citizens for Participation in Political Action (CPPAX), 1989-1990 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - City University of New York, "Socialist Scholars Conference", 1986 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Coalición para las Necesidades Basicas Humanas, Undated (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights, 1989-1991 (Box 87, Folder 7a)
  - Coalition for the Legal Rights of the Disabled (CLRD), 1985-1990 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Coalition of Welcoming Congregations (CWC), Circa 2005 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Commission on Social Action of Reform Judaism, 1996 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Government Operations, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Common Bond Ink, 1985-1989 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Community Pride Reporter, 1998 June (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Community Unity Boston, Undated (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Community Works, 1997 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Concerned Maine Families, Circa 1995 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Connecticut Women's Education and Legal Fund (CWEALF), 1989, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Cornell University Library, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Dignity USA, 2005 December (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Education in a Disabled Gay Environment (EDGE), 1988 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Emerge, 1980, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Equal Rights Advocates, Inc., Undated (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Equal Rights Center, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Equality Maine (EQME), Equality News, 2006 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Equality Press, 2002 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Equity Foundation, Undated (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Evangelicals Concerned, Inc., 1982 (Box 87, Folder 13)